<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
 <post id="MS_9203_42423204">
      <user id="MS_12503923">
        <username>Fireman Deluxe.....Start Learning Russian Folks</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>56</age>
        <city>LEEDS</city>
        <province>New York</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1209751620</date>
      <body>a href="http://www.msplinks.com/MDFodHRwOi8vd3d3Lm15c3BhY2UuY29tL2 dlb3JnaWxsYXRoZWdvcmlsbGE=" target="new"&gt;.:The Red Pills Gorilla:.    &lt;/center&gt;   This is going to be a hard pill to swallow if it's your first one but if you're ready let's do it.  You, your friends and your family need to know this.  It is coming up very quick too, you don't have much time. I would present this in a softer manner but the next stage of this plan goes into action in May 2008. That's when we get the ID cards with chips.  Welcome to a Brave New World.    &lt;center&gt;  RFID is Here to Stay Like it or Not           Add to My Profile   &lt;/center&gt;  Watch Aaron Russo's (창&#153;짜 RIP 창&#153;짜) ..America: Freedom to Fascism.., it explains a LOT about what's going on and connects a lot of concepts that you need to know about. He explains the fraud of income tax and that they have been deceiving us since 1913. He basically establishes that Congress has had the power and obligation to repeal the Federal Income Tax the whole time because it's a scam. Well....if they are doing that...what else are they doing?..... &lt;center&gt;            &lt;bIG&gt;How RFID works&lt;/bIG&gt;        &lt;/center&gt;  Microchips are ALREADY in passports. Did you know that? They use RFID in hospitals now, they just strap it to the babies leg for "security". They use it for criminals, companies, the elderly or "Wander Prone" This may seem like a "Noooo way" kinda thing...but they are already using it and WE MUST FIGHT AT ALL COSTS TO REPEL MANDATORY INJECTION!&lt;center&gt;&lt;bIG&gt;   RFID: Tracking Everything Part 1          The Rest of the Series     Operation Lie and Deceive Verichip Style           Add to My Profile        Verichip and North American Union : The Truth           IBM, VERICHIP and the FOURTH REICH           Add to My Profile     ..  &lt;center&gt;&lt;bIG&gt;  To save ANY YouTube Video:&lt;/bIG&gt;  Get the URL from the video.    Go to www. savetube. com  Put in the URL, click go.    This will generate a link.    Click it.    This will go to where your default files go  Go rename it "Title.  flv"  You need a Flash Video Player to watch it  THEN  UPLOAD back into your own account!   &lt;bIG&gt;BOYCOTT ALL CORPORATE MAINSTREAM MEDIA!  &lt;bIG&gt;BECOME THE MEDIA!  </body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9203_42425324">
      <user id="MS_85600535">
        <username>MOJAVEBLUE</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>38</age>
        <city>Oregon</city>
        <province/>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1209754620</date>
      <body>How about (1) LInk~ pick your fav. then when i get there , the rest can be &lt;clicked&gt; ???? i appreciate your post and the info. Looks Like it is time for mankind to start making Serious Decisions.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9203_42438559">
      <user id="MS_12503923">
        <username>Fireman Deluxe.....Start Learning Russian Folks</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>56</age>
        <city>LEEDS</city>
        <province>New York</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1209787740</date>
      <body>With myspace screwing around with the links, I couldn't figure how to post this so I posted all of it</body>
    </post>
</posts> 
